This is what we will be in after getting braces.  I hadn't
thought of it.  Yes sir.  So as soon as I
wake up in the morning, I reach the gym and start
building my body.  And today I had to
use all my strength with my hands.
Yes, I mean, if I didn't have braces, I would have used them
with my teeth.  Well,
while coming back I will bring milk and bread from the shop.
Yes, because the doctor has
asked me to eat only soft food for a week.  Then I
make strong bay leaf tea with my own hands.
Then Dolo and I sit together and
have nice tea and bread.  But if this did
not satisfy my hunger, I would simply sit down and eat dal and rice.
But there was a lot of difficulty in chewing it.
Because now there was a
little pain in the teeth also.  So I come
straight out of the water.  Well, in the evening we check
whether our teeth have become straight or
not.  And there is no noticeable twitching in the teeth of the dolls.
But my tooth which
was on the inside has become completely straight in just one day.
Yes, in this happiness
I take a pain killer.  And then
both of us demand mom to prepare something nice for dinner.
Yes, because
Dolo has also developed a couple of blisters in his mouth.
Then, as soon as it is time for dinner in the evening,
Hitler Didi
brings a bowl full of vermicelli for us.  Yes, I have
brought it because mom made it.
So let's go and eat vermicelli.  Rest you can
tell us in the comments what else we should eat in soft food.